Guide to the Daniel Coit Gilman Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Special Files, 1850-1910; Series III; .75 linear feet (2 boxes)
  - Memorabilia, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - New Charter - New President Yale newspaper clippings, 1870-1871 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - New International Encyclopeadia Review, 1902 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Photo Album (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Reminicences of Willys Warner's connection with raising Yale funds, 1864 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Sheffield Scientific School, 1864, 1871 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Tributes, Biographical Materials, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Tributes and obituaries, Biographical Material, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Winchester Observatory (correspondence and landgrant), 1871 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - "Woman's Rights" newspaper clippings, 1850-1857 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Yale Corp. proposed change in the Corp., notes, 1871 (Box 7, Folder 21)